Grant, Alice, Additional Records /4095
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alice Grant Additional Records
1949-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Grant, Alice
/4095
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Records (documents).
7984563
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 22, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Alice Grant was a labor educator and staff member of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University.
Grant earned her B.A. from Wells College and an M.A. from Cornell University. She worked as education director for the Rochester Joint Board of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) before joining the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations as director of the Rochester Extension office in 1963. Grant held that position until she passed away on November 17, 1988, at the age of 66.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3005: Alice Grant Papers
Grant, Alice, 1922-1988; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
7984563
- Arbitration #1 (Box 1)
  - Association of Flight Attendants (AFA)-United Airlines - Unsorted, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AFA-United - Dawn Casey, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AFA-United Airlines - Mattox, 1949-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AFA-United - Kimuu Case, 1967-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes four black and white photographs
  - AFA-United Airlines 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AFA-United Airlines 1979, 1972-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Airlines - Association of Professional Flight Attendants (APFA), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - APFA-American Airlines 1984, 1969-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union (ATU)-Binghamton 1988, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ATU-Binghamton 1987, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ATU-Rochester Transit 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE)-Batavia, Virginia 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AFGE-Immigration Service 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME)-Council 82 Administration, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania-AFSCME Panel, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME-Buffalo Board of Education 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME-Geneva 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME-Geriatric Center, Erie, Pennsylvania, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME-County of Monroe 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME Council 82-Erie County 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME Council 82-Erie 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - AFSCME Council 82-Orleans County 1986, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Arbitration #2 (Box 2)
  - AFSCME-Batavia 1986, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME-Buffalo 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME-Erie County 1985 (time off for union business), 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME-Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)-Erie County 1983, 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME-Meadville 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME-Meadville 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME-North Tonawanda 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME-State of Pennsylvania - Rossi 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME-Syracuse 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME-Pennsylvania - Keck 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME-New York State Department of Correctional Services - Peters 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME-Geneseo 1981, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Includes news clippings
  - AFSCME-Rochester 1986, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME-Rochester 1986 - Van Auken, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - AFSCME-Rochester City School District 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME Council 66-Niagara Housing Authority 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME-City of Rochester - Lewis Petote 1987, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME-Rochester - Fred Head 1987, 1975-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME-Rochester - Randy Gates 1987, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME-Rochester - Stark 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Local 866-Binghamton Schools 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - CSEA-Corning Painted Post School District 1988, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - CSEA-Elmira 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - CSEA-Onondaga County 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - CSEA-Onondaga County 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - CSEA-Niagara 1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - CSEA-Richburg 1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - CSEA-Seneca Falls Schools 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - CSEA-Town of Evans, 1979-1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - CSEA-Hudson Valley Community College 1977, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Arbitration award was handed down January 3, 1978
  - CSEA-Genesee County 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - CSEA-Horseheads Central School District, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - CSEA-Monroe County 1985 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - CSEA-Monroe County 1984, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - CSEA-Monroe County 1982, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Arbitration #3 (Box 3)
  - CSEA-Monroe County 1981, 1971-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CSEA-Monroe County 1980, 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CSEA-Monroe County 1977, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - CSEA-Monroe County 1974, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - CSEA-Newark 1988, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - CSEA-Olean 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CSEA-Seneca County 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CSEA-West Seneca 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Town of West Seneca-CSEA - Case Number A78-316, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Communication Workers of America (CWA)-Arnot-Ogden Memorial Hospital 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CWA-Elmira Hospital 1980, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CWA-DeGraff Hospital 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Erie Community College Administrators-Erie County 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Firefighters-Buffalo 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers Union-Welch Foods 1985, 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Grain Millers-General Mills 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE)-Holiday Inn 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - HERE and NOW-Rochester United Methodist Home 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1199C - Hahnemann 1983, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW)-Afro-Lecon 1983, 1974-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Clarification concerning the 1983 ruling was requested January 5, 1984
  - IAMAW-Allis-Chalmers Corporation 1984, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    A letter concerning the instructions of the 1984 ruling was sent January 23, 1985
  - IAM-AIMCO 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    The IAM is equivalent to the IAMAW
  - IAMAW-Allis-Chalmers Corporation 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - IAM-J.D. Cousins 1983 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - IAM-J.D. Cousins 1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - IAM-Dustex Corporation 1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - IAMAW-Harley Davidson 1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - IAM-Loud-Wendel 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - IAMAW-McGraw Edison Service 1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - IAMAW Local 630, District 76-Mckenica Inc., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - IAMAW-Precision Components 1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - IAM-Roblin Steel 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - IAM-Rome Cable 1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Independent Union of Porcelain Workers-Ervite Corporation 1978 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW)-AVX Ceramics 1982 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - IBEW-New York Power Authority 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - IBEW-Pennsylvania Power and Light Company 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Includes four color photographs and an architectural print entered as exhibits during the arbitration hearing
  - IBEW-General Telephone 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - IBEW-General Telephone 1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - IBEW-Niagara Falls 1984, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Includes an architectural print
  - Iron Workers - Northern Steel Corporation 1977 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Buffalo Typographical Union (BTU)-Buffalo Courier Express 1979 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE)-Ameron 1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - IUE-Consolidated Packaging Machinery 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - IUE-Dollinger 1986, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - IUE-Dollinger 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Dollinger-IUE 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - IUE-Dollinger 1975 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - IUE-Uniflow 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Arbitration #4 (Box 4)
  - IUE-Ryerson Steel 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - IUE-R.T. Jones 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - IUE-R.T. Jones 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Laborers International Union of North America-Council of Utility Contractors and Traylor Brothers 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Laborers-Austin Company 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Licensed Practical Nurses and Technicians (LPN)-The Health Care Plan, Inc. 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - LPN-Onondaga County 1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - New York State Nurses Association-Erie County 1987, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Guild-Buffalo Courier Express 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Niagara Hooker Employees Union-Hooker Chemical 1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Meat Cutters-Russer Foods 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - New York State Nurses Association- Erie County 1984, 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW)-Allied Chemical Corporation 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - OCAW-Airco Speer Carbon-Graphite 1980, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - OCAW-Carborundum Company 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - OCAW-Morton Salt 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - OCAW-Niagara Steel 1975, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Includes five color photographs
  - OCAW-Quaker State Oil 1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Operating Engineers-National Trailer Company (Kreuger Co.) 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Includes an agreement between the International Union of Operating Engineers and Western New York Construction Machinery Suppliers, Inc.
  - International Union of Operating Engineers (OEIU)-Heckett Division of Harsco Corporation 1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU)-Blue Cross 1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - OPEIU-FMC Corporation 1984, 1960-1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - OPEIU Local 212-Worthington Compressors, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Paper handlers Local Union-Arcata Graphics, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Includes seven black and white photographs (one photograph, from a series of eight, seems to be missing); includes a map of the Arcata Graphics Buffalo plant
  - Professional, Clerical and Technical Employees Association-Buffalo Board of Education 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Public Employees Federation (PEF)-United Field Representatives and Staff Union 1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - PEF-New York State Department of Social Services 1982, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Includes news clippings0
  - United Paperworkers International Union - Container Corporation of America 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Plumbers (United Association Local Union)-Mechanical Contractors Association of Rochester 1984 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Buffalo Police Benevolent Association (PBA)-City of Buffalo 1988, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - North Tonawanda PBA-City of North Tonawanda 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Rochester Police Locust Club- City of Rochester1977, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Rochester Police Locust Club-City of Rochester 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Includes news clippings reporting on the arbitration decision
  - Police (Webster 1000 Club)-Town of Webster 1979 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Red Jacket Police Club-Town of West Seneca 1977 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Some number of pages from the conclusion section of the arbitration final report seem to be missing
  - Retail Clerks-Bell Supermarket 1982 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Retail Clerks-Millward Alloys 1981 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Building Service Employees International Union (SEIU)-City of DuBois 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - SEIU-Veterans Administration Hospital, Canandaigua, New York 1982, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - United Steel Workers of America (USWA)-Abex Corporation 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - USWA-Arco Metals Company 1985, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - USWA-Allied Chemical 1985 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - USWA-Buffalo Forge Company 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - USWA-Copperweld Corporation 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - USWA-Great Lakes Carbon Corporation 1984, 1969-1984 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - USWA-Great Lakes Carbon Corporation 1977, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - USWA-Dresser Industries 1974 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - USWA-Koppers Company 1983 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - USWA-Kurlash Diamond 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - USWA-0-CEL-0 General Mills, Inc. 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Arbitration #5 (Box 5)
  - USWA-Purity Baking Company 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - USWA-PEMCOR, Inc. 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - USWA-Roberts-Gordon Appliance Corporation 1988, 1982-1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - USWA-Roberts-Gordon Appliance Corporation 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Includes two color photographs
  - USWA-Worthington 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters-General Crushed Stone Company 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters-General Foods 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters-Hertz 1976, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Includes four color photographs; incudes a drawn map of a parking lot
  - Teamsters-Lee-Norse Company 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters-Metalstand 1982, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Teamsters-Pan Am 1978, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Includes copies of three different black and white photographs
  - Teamsters-Morgan Services 1987, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Trans World Airlines (TWA)-Paul F. Sanborn 1984, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - TWA-Linda Turner 1976, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Transport Workers Union (TWU)-Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority (SEPTA) 1987, 1966-1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - TWU-SEPTA 1985, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - TWU-SEPTA 1986 (Travel Time), 1976-1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - TWU-SEPTA 1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW)-AMSCO 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - UAW-AMSCO 1974, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Includes post hearing briefs
  - UAW-Buick 1985, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - UAW-Bartlett Buick 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - UAW-Condec 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - UAW-Curtis Screw Company 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - UAW-Delavan 1982 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - United Airlines Arbitration Board Scheduling and Miscellany (Unsorted), 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Includes several photographs and articles clipped from a magazine; items in folder were found loose in the box
- Arbitration #6 (Box 6)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW)-Delavan 1981, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - UAW-Fairchild Republic Company 1980, 1957-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Includes a map of an airplane pad; includes 13 black and white photographs
  - UAW-Kramer Volkswagen 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - UAW-Niagara Lockport 1982, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - UAW-Niagara Machine and Tool 1981, 1971-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - UAW-Reed Manufacturing Company 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - UAW-Skinner 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - UAW-Snyder Tank Corporation 1984, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    The award was handed down January 2, 1985
  - UAW-Snyder Tank Corporation 1984 (II), 1979-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Includes post-hearing letters
  - UAW-Snyder Tank Corporation 1977, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - UAW-Taylor Chevrolet 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE)-GE 1986, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service Administration of Cases, 1976-1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service-National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service - American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service-Mailhandlers 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - United Paperworkers International Union (UPIU)-Banner Fibreboard Company 1975, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - UPIU-Westvaco 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - United Rubber Workers (URW)-Mohawk Rubber Company 1984, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Education-3020a cases, 1977-1983 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Addison Teachers 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Addison Teachers 1980, 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Addison Teachers 1979, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Addison Teachers 1978, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Arbitration #7 (Box 7)
  - Altmar-Parish-Williamstown Teachers 1988, 1975-1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Amsterdam Teachers 1980, 1968-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Amsterdam Teachers 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Board of Cooperative Educational Services (BOCES) Teachers (Steuben-Allegany) 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Teachers 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Central United Employees Association 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bradford Teachers 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Brockport Teachers 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Binghamton Teacher 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Teachers Federation-Buffalo Board of Education 1971, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Folder contains a second grievance case from 1972
  - Canajoharie Central School Support Personnel 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Teachers 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Cheektowaga Teachers 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Churchville-Chili Education Association and Churchville-Chili Central School District 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Churchville-Chili Teachers 1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Clinton Teachers 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Schuyler-Chemung Tioga BOCES 1982, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Cohoes Teachers 1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Corning Teachers 1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dansville Teachers 1988, 1980-1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Depew Teachers 1973, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - East Rochester Teachers 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - East Rochester Teachers 1974, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Elmira Teachers 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Elmira Teachers 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Elmira Teachers 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Elmira School District-Custodial Union 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Elmira Custodial 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Erie Community College-New York Education Association (NYEA)1980, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - NYEA-Erie Community College 1982, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Folder contains another grievance report from 1987
  - Faculty Federation of Erie Community College Teachers-County of Erie 1979, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Erie Teachers 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Fall River Teachers 1980, 1965-1980 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Fairport Teachers 1975, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Arbitration #8 (Box 8)
  - Gloversville Teachers Association 1980, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Greece Teachers 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Greece Teachers 1987, 1983-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Homer Teachers 1986, 1974-1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Honeoye Teachers Association 1988, 1973-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Horseheads Teachers 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Horsehead Teachers 1980, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Horsehead Teachers 1979, 1972-1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Horsehead Teachers 1977, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Falconer Teachers 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Honeoye New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) non-teachers 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lackawanna Teachers 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lyndonville Teachers 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Mayville Teachers 1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Niagara Falls Teachers 1981, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - New York Mills Teachers 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - North Colonie Teachers 1984, 1976-1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - North Tonawanda Teachers 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Odessa-Montour Teachers 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Arbitration #9 unsorted (Box 9)
  - South Seneca Teachers 1985, 1975-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration: Spencerport Teachers, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Spencerport Teachers 1983, 1976-1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Spencerport Teachers 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Susquehanna Teachers 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Tonawanda Teachers 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Tully Teachers 1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Utica Teachers 1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Waterloo Teachers 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Waterloo Teachers 1980 (II), 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Watkins Glenn Teachers 1975, 1967-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Waverly Teachers 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Webster Teachers 1982, 1977-1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - West Irondequoit Teachers 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - West Seneca Teachers 1978, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Wheatland-Chili Teachers 1977, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Williamsville Teachers 1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Non-teachers Unit NYSUT-Alden 1984, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Arbitration #10 unsorted (Box 10)
  - Schuylerville Teachers 1985, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Solvay Teachers 1981, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Sonye-New York Education Association (NYEA)1981, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Philadelphia Teachers 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Teachers 1988, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia Teachers 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Rush-Henrietta Teachers 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Schalmont Teachers 1987, 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Owego Teachers 1982, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Owego Teachers 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Oswego Administrators 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Pavilion Teachers 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Pen Yan Teachers 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Phelps-Clifton Springs Employees Association 1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Troy Firefighters 1985, 1977-1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Interest Arbitration: Lockport-Hickory Club Police Benevolent Association (PBA) 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Norwich Fire Fighters Interest Arbitration 1984, 1977-1984 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Oswego Fire Fighters Interest Arbitration 1983, 1975-1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Interest Arbitration East Rochester Police 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - East Aurora Police Benevolent Association 1984, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Includes post-settlement letters
  - Hamburg Police 1984 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Lackawanna Police 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Office Files (Box 11)
  - American Arbitration Association (AAA) Advisory Council, 1982-1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee, 1972-1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Brockport, 1971-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Brockport-Marcus, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Credit Courses, 1976-1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rochester Staff Meetings, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Labor Management Center, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Public Employment Relations Board (PERB) Conferences, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)